Privacy Policy
==============

**TheSixthAxis Online Privacy Statement**
-----------------------------------------

TheSixthAxis Online recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of TheSixthAxis.com (TheSixthAxis). We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users’ right to privacy.

### **General**

TheSixthAxis uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsible third parties after permission from the user.

TheSixthAxis is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which we may provide links or the websites of our affiliates or advertisers.

### **Use of Information**

TheSixthAxis does not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission.

TheSixthAxis uses users’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. We may combine demographic information supplied by a subscriber at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information with our advertisers to help them better understand our services, but TheSixthAxis does not give advertisers information about individual users of TheSixthAxis.

TheSixthAxis uses cookies to deliver content specific to users’ interests and to honor their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our users.

### Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that this Website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data, first name, last name, email address and username.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this Website.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Website is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this Website to provide its services. In cases where this Website specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Website or by the owners of third-party services used by this Website serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Website and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

Mode and place of processing the Data
-------------------------------------

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this Website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

* Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
* provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
* processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
* processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
* processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User’s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User’s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

### Retention time

Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

Therefore:

* Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
* Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

### The purposes of processing

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, SPAM protection, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Advertising, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Content commenting, Displaying content from external platforms, Interaction with online survey platforms, Registration and authentication, Social features and Contacting the User.

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
-------------------------------------------------------

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Advertising

We use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may be served from our third party advertiser. You can view their [privacy policy](https://www.network-n.com/network-privacy-policy/) and [cookie policy](https://www.network-n.com/network-cookie-policy/) here. You can manage your cookies here: [Manage Cookie Settings](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/privacy-policy/?cmpscreen)

We use Google Analytics and Comscore to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics and Comscore gather information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Comscore’s privacy policy is available at [https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy](https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy).

#### Google AdSense (Google LLC)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google LLC. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout). Privacy Shield participant.

#### OpenX Ad Exchange (OpenX Technologies, Inc.)

OpenX Ad Exchange is an advertising service provided by OpenX Technologies, Inc.  
The service provides an ad exchange platform that facilitates the optimization of ads from multiple ad networks, which can be third parties to both OpenX and the Owner.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://openx.com/legal/ad-exchange-privacy-principles/) – [Opt Out](http://openx.com/legal/).

#### Rubicon Project (The Rubicon Project, Inc.)

Rubicon Project is an advertising service provided by The Rubicon Project, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/).

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google LLC)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google LLC (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Privacy Shield participant.

### Contacting the User

#### Mailing list or newsletter (this Website)

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Website. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Website or after making a purchase.

Personal Data collected: email address.

### Content commenting

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Website.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.

#### Comment system managed directly (this Website)

This Website has its own internal content comment system.

Personal Data collected: email address, first name, last name and username.

### Displaying content from external platforms

This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### Google Fonts (Google LLC)

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google LLC that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)

Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://instagram.com/legal/privacy/).

#### Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC)

Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://vimeo.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### YouTube video widget (Google LLC)

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google LLC that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Gravatar (Automattic Inc.)

Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter’s email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar – even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.

Personal Data collected: email address and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).

### Hosting and backend infrastructure

This type of service has the purpose of hosting Data and files that enable this Website to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of this Website. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

#### Amazon Web Services (AWS) (Amazon Web Services, Inc.)

Amazon Web Services is a hosting and backend service provided by Amazon.com Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United Kingdom – [Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/). Privacy Shield participant.

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.  
The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google LLC)

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

### Interaction with online survey platforms

This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party online survey platforms directly from the pages of this Website.  
If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service.

#### Polldaddy Widget (Polldaddy Ltd.)

The Polldaddy Widget is a service for interacting with the Polldaddy online survey platform provided by Polldaddy Ltd.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: Ireland – [Privacy Policy](https://polldaddy.com/privacy/).

### Registration and authentication

By registering or authenticating, Users allow this Website to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.  
Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, this Website will be able to access some Data, stored by these third-party services, for registration or identification purposes.

#### Direct registration (this Website)

The User registers by filling out the registration form and providing the Personal Data directly to this Website.

Personal Data collected: email address, first name, last name and username.

### Social features

#### Public profile (this Website)

Users may have public profiles that other Users can display. In addition to the Personal Data provided, this profile may contain Users’ interactions with this Website.

Personal Data collected: username.

### SPAM protection

This type of service analyzes the traffic of this Website, potentially containing Users’ Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.

#### Google reCAPTCHA (Google LLC)

Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google LLC.  
The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Privacy Shield participant.

Further information about Personal Data
---------------------------------------

### Gleam.io

Personal Data: email address and cookies

https://gleam.io/privacy

### Forums

TheSixthAxis makes message boards available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Use of Information

TheSixthAxis does not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission.

TheSixthAxis uses users’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. We may combine demographic information supplied by a subscriber at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information with our advertisers to help them better understand our services, but TheSixthAxis does not give advertisers information about individual users of TheSixthAxis.

TheSixthAxis uses cookies to deliver content specific to users’ interests and to honor their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our users.

### Information collected by TheSixthAxis

TheSixthAxis collects information about users during their registration for our newsletter and during their participation in certain activities on our website, including contests. When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users.

### General

TheSixthAxis uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsible third parties after permission from the user.

TheSixthAxis is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which we may provide links or the websites of our affiliates or advertisers.

### Opt Out

TheSixthAxis provides users the following opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor, and upon request: Email [\[email protected\]](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Correct/Update

TheSixthAxis provides users the following opportunity for changing and modifying information previously provided: Email [\[email protected\]](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

The rights of Users
-------------------

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

* **Withdraw their consent at any time.** Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
* **Object to processing of their Data.** Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
* **Access their Data.** Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
* **Verify and seek rectification.** Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
* **Restrict the processing of their Data.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
* **Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
* **Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.** Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
* **Lodge a complaint.** Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

### Details about the right to object to processing

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

Additional information about Data collection and processing
-----------------------------------------------------------

### Legal action

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User’s Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Website (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### How “Do Not Track” requests are handled

This Website does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

#### User

The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

#### Data Subject

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Website.

#### This Website (or this Application)

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

#### Service

The service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

#### European Union (or EU)

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

### **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computers hard drive. Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

We use cookies on thesixthaxis.com to make sure we give you the best experience possible on the site. If you continue browsing the site without changing your settings, we will assume that you’re happy to receive all cookies on this website. If you would like to change your cookie settings at any time here are instructions how to do this for a variety of browsers (however blocking all cookies will have a negative impact with website usability):

Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en  
Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences  
Opera: http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/  
Internet Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-deletemanage-cookies  
Safari: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411  
Edge: https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy

**Correct/Update**

TheSixthAxis provides users the following opportunity for changing and modifying information previously provided:  
Email [\[email protected\]](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Owner and Data Controller
-------------------------

TheSixthAxis C/O The Three Mariners  
Bridge Lane  
Lancaster  
LA1 1EE  
United Kingdom

**Owner contact email:** [\[email protected\]](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Legal information

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.

Latest update: January 28, 2020

Copyright © 2024 TheSixthAxis Site By [MCA](https://www.magentoecommerceagency.co.uk/)

We do not license content or design to any other site. No element of this site can be used without written permission. All content should be considered opinion. Article posters are the individual owner of the article content. We are not affiliated with any third party.

Use of this website is subject to acceptance of our [legal terms of service](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/about/). [Staff / Contact Us](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/staff/) | [Review Policy](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/review-policy/) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/privacy-policy/) | [Cookies Policy](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cookies-policy/) – [Manage Cookie Settings](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/privacy-policy/?cmpscreen)

Advertising and PR: [\[email protected\]](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) | News: [\[email protected\]](https://www.thesixthaxis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) TheSixthAxis is featured on: [Metacritic](http://www.metacritic.com/games/), [OpenCritic](https://opencritic.com/outlet/68/thesixthaxis), [vrgamecritic](https://vrgamecritic.com/publication/1064), [Google News](https://news.google.com/news/search?aq=f&pz=1&cf=all&ned=uk&hl=en&q=thesixthaxis) | listed on: [NewsNow](http://www.newsnow.co.uk/nn/TheSixthAxiscom)
